groovinads.com 2013-05-24

# Privacy Policy | GroovinAds

Date: August 17, 2010   
GroovinAds respects your privacy. This document provides information about the data GroovinAds stores and how it is used. Groovinads is a product of OsAdsPro SRL and its subsidiaries.

**About GroovinAds**  

GroovinAds provides an intelligent ad serving service to advertisers, media publishers, marketing agencies, affiliates and ad networks. The service displays banners that communicate our advertisers offers across the publishers sites, affiliated sites or ad networks where their campaigns run.

**Storing personal information**  

GroovinAds doesn’t store personal information from the users our ads target. The service doesn’t know their name, ID number, address, telephone number or any information that may identify them personally. 

**Cookies**  

GroovinAds uses cookies to provide their customers with reports on the number of unique users that the saw the ads or visited their website. The use of cookies is an industry standard. A cookie is a file that is stored on your computer and is checked by the site or service that stored it there whenever the data is needed. Most browsers have an option to disable cookies. The information stored in the cookie GroovinAds uses is only an encrypted unique identifier. The cookie is set with an expiration date of 30 days. If you wish to disable cookies from GroovinAds, please visit the [opt-out](http://www.groovinads.com/en/optout) page. Remember you must have cookies enabled in your browser for the [opt-out](http://www.groovinads.com/optout) process to work. 

**Anonymous  **

GroovinAds stores anonymous information from users accessing web sites or their clients campaigns. This information may include:  
* View information about campaigns   
* Information about visits to the advertiser\’s web pages   
* Information about the interaction with the banners

Generally each record stores the cookie ID, the user’s IP address and browser type.

The stored information allows us to provide our customers with reports of their campaigns and traffic sent to their website. These reports can even include the number of unique cookies that interacted with each campaign or visited the advertiser\’s website.

**Geolocalization**

GroovinAds uses geolocalization technology to determine the user’s location based on their IP address. The technology is then used to target campaigns based on country, region or city. Eg. It could choose to show a campaign from a pharmacy in the city of Miami only to users of that city.  
GroovinAds also uses geolocation technology to provide their customers with traffic reports by city, region and country.

**Protected information**

GroovinAds stores the information with the purpose of providing its customers with campaign performance reports or number of visits to their web sites, and the information is also used to boost the campaign’s performance. Each client has an account on GroovinAds.com and no information is shared between different client accounts. 

**Changes to this policy**

GroovinAds may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on his website. You should access this page frequently to make sure you are aware of any changes.

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact:

OsAdsPro S.R.L.  
Borges 2802, Vicente Lopez CP1636  
Prov. de Buenos Aires  
Argentina
